<?xml version="1.0"?>
<forum type="reddit">
<thread id="30zbtu">
<category>movies</category>
<posts>
<post id="cpx9gwv">
<author>noodlescb</author>
<timestamp>1427846410</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7cm3</parentid>
<body>I hope the April Fools joke is that they are making a sequel to that shitbag of a movie.</body>
<upvotes>9</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9h7n">
<author>noodlescb</author>
<timestamp>1427846424</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7zhx</parentid>
<body>Be hard to make it worse</body>
<upvotes>10</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9lll">
<author>Darthspud</author>
<timestamp>1427846638</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9euf</parentid>
<body>Also, one day we *might* get a crisis movie where both universes meet. Nothing could be more awesome.</body>
<upvotes>21</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9oyg">
<author>AwesomeGuy847</author>
<timestamp>1427846801</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7q1m</parentid>
<body>For now. Give it time and she'll improve.</body>
<upvotes>16</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9qig">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427846875</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>[deleted]</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9row">
<author>laymness</author>
<timestamp>1427846929</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>You've failed this sewer.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9s3u">
<author>ericspeaker</author>
<timestamp>1427846949</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Now I have to watch the first new TMNT movie so I'll be ready for Amell in the second.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9seg">
<author>ParkerZA</author>
<timestamp>1427846963</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9gwv</parentid>
<body>The movie that grossed $485 million? Yeah, wtf is wrong with them.</body>
<upvotes>29</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9six">
<author>Vercadi</author>
<timestamp>1427846968</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx70sm</parentid>
<body>Have you seen it?</body>
<upvotes>10</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9udo">
<author>Doro1234</author>
<timestamp>1427847060</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9amr</parentid>
<body>I feel they should have gone makeup instead of CG on Azog. Manu would have really gotten the ability to show off his acting in that capacity.</body>
<upvotes>9</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpx9vit">
<author>The_Asian_Hamster</author>
<timestamp>1427847114</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Dont know the character... is he more a serious character like Arrow, or more fun?</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxa30f">
<author>DrazahNede</author>
<timestamp>1427847478</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7dnd</parentid>
<body>The CW is great for genre television. Jane the Virgin, The 100, Arrow, The Flash and (so far) iZombie are really good shows and break the Gossip Girl and Pretty Little Liars stereotype.</body>
<upvotes>5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxa3ot">
<author>CageyTurtlez</author>
<timestamp>1427847513</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9udo</parentid>
<body>They absolutely should have gone prosthetic makeup, I don't get how a studio that brought Gollum and Smaug to life could make CGI orcs look like such ass.</body>
<upvotes>8</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxa8l4">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427847755</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>I'd be more excited over this, but they killed off TJ Miller pretty quickly in the previous movie. And Will Arnett was terribly underused.

So yeah, my expectations are still in the gutter as far as the human characters go. So all I'll be expecting is that he'll make the terrible script as tolerable as possible.

Edit: I forgot TJ Miller was in Transformers 4 and not TMNT, also different directors. But even if Michael Bay didn't direct TMNT, it still feels like a Michael Bay movie with the trend of shitty human characters.</body>
<upvotes>-1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxabr1">
<author>SoulxxBondz</author>
<timestamp>1427847904</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Hopefully he'll do as well as Elias Koteas, who was probably the best Casey Jones of them all. Favorite character in the original movies.</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxahi3">
<author>IwishIwasGoku</author>
<timestamp>1427848179</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7dnd</parentid>
<body>Yeah, and they're looking to expand more and more by the looks of it. They got a new spinoff team-up coming and possibly ties to Supergirl and Titans. Plus the non-comic shows they're launching are better than they used to be as well. Really improving as a network. Not award-worthy, but who knows where they'll be in 5 years.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxaiqm">
<author>Tobias_you_blowhard</author>
<timestamp>1427848239</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7dnd</parentid>
<body>Yeah I don't what happened but CW has been stepping it up in recent years. Arrow and Flash are awesome, and iZombie has actually been really good too. I hear some of their other shows are getting good reviews as well.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxajv6">
<author>iamthegraham</author>
<timestamp>1427848293</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9lll</parentid>
<body>Holy shit that would rule.</body>
<upvotes>11</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxasgh">
<author>Kilgeralt</author>
<timestamp>1427848708</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9euf</parentid>
<body>&gt;Second, I'd rather they keep the movie and TV universe separate? Why? Because it allows both shows freedom to do whatever they want. The TV version can cast and use major villains without worrying about how it will interfere with the cinematic universe.
To give an example, Agents of Shield can't use bigger villains in the show because the movies might use them. If the movies are using them, they will prefer to cast more well established actors for the role that TV can't afford. Robert Downey Jr isn't going to commit to a season long arc of a TV show when he can get paid 10 times of that by working a fraction of the time.

A character on Arrow was recently phased out because that same character is appearing in one of DC's new movies.</body>
<upvotes>9</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxatdy">
<author>THE_ULTIMATE_RAPIST</author>
<timestamp>1427848753</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx74nn</parentid>
<body>10/10 comment m8</body>
<upvotes>4</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxaw5b">
<author>HouseNinja</author>
<timestamp>1427848883</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>That's gonna cost you, Tinkerbell</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxawx3">
<author>bradpax10</author>
<timestamp>1427848920</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxasgh</parentid>
<body>Who? Deadshot?</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxay9o">
<author>RustyDetective</author>
<timestamp>1427848983</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Although I do not support the new TMNT, I am very glad for him.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxazs2">
<author>NotEnoughGun</author>
<timestamp>1427849056</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9seg</parentid>
<body>It's like they want to make money or something, it's sickening.</body>
<upvotes>21</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxb14g">
<author>Kilgeralt</author>
<timestamp>1427849122</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxawx3</parentid>
<body>[spoilers](#s "Yes.")</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxb20g">
<author>emilskoda</author>
<timestamp>1427849167</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7t06</parentid>
<body>that guy is always on point</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxb2qo">
<author>twent4</author>
<timestamp>1427849203</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7ba3</parentid>
<body>a buddy of mine that goes to every comic expo he can (edmonton, calgary, san diego are his recent ones) says he snubs all of them. Not sure if it's because of his schedule or personality.</body>
<upvotes>-18</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxb2tv">
<author>salmalight</author>
<timestamp>1427849207</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx6ury</parentid>
<body>If the Internet has taught me anything, it's that everyone is a lier.</body>
<upvotes>-1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxb8ur">
<author>spiritbearr</author>
<timestamp>1427849497</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxawx3</parentid>
<body>Odd since Captain Boomerang is also in Suicide Squad but then again if they do go multi verse I want Ashur and Varo fighting.</body>
<upvotes>7</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbaq1">
<author>schmidtopolis</author>
<timestamp>1427849586</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxb2qo</parentid>
<body>Snubs them like he doesn't make appearances? Or he's a dick to fans?

Because if it's the former, he doesn't owe anyone a damn thing beyond his work on the show.</body>
<upvotes>9</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbbko">
<author>noodlescb</author>
<timestamp>1427849627</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9seg</parentid>
<body>Good point. Money is God. Forgot my place.</body>
<upvotes>-11</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbm4f">
<author>sthrn</author>
<timestamp>1427850137</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Oh good, another one.</body>
<upvotes>-2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbpe4">
<author>PM_me_movie_scripts</author>
<timestamp>1427850296</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7cm3</parentid>
<body>An April O'Neil Fools joke! 


I'll show myself out.</body>
<upvotes>30</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbub2">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427850537</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>[deleted]</body>
<upvotes>-5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbwdh">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427850637</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9h7n</parentid>
<body>[deleted]</body>
<upvotes>6</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxbz3a">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427850762</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxbub2</parentid>
<body>People pretending the guy who portrays Green Arrow will portray Green Arrow in TMNT, and possibly somehow bring the people who wrote his character in the TV series to also write his character in the movie.</body>
<upvotes>-5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxc52z">
<author>Sugreev2001</author>
<timestamp>1427851043</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx8gfb</parentid>
<body>Both are far better than the Smallville Clark-Lana subplot</body>
<upvotes>6</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxc87l">
<author>Dynamiklol</author>
<timestamp>1427851192</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx6zlx</parentid>
<body>Who the fuck cares? It's Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxc8un">
<author>OMGALEX</author>
<timestamp>1427851221</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9gwv</parentid>
<body>I can 100% gurantee that you haven't seen it, man.</body>
<upvotes>5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcjdh">
<author>pjtheman</author>
<timestamp>1427851720</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7zk5</parentid>
<body>ARROW FLASH FIRESTORM AND ATOM ARE GONNA BE IN THE NEXT EPISODE!  ITS LIKE AN EARLY STAGE OF THE JUSTICE LEAGUE</body>
<upvotes>5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcknl">
<author>pjtheman</author>
<timestamp>1427851780</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7xg4</parentid>
<body>Manu Bennett would like a word with you.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcli0">
<author>RedBarrel</author>
<timestamp>1427851820</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Didn't think they'd get me interested in this movie, but they did. He seems like a good fit for my favorite TMNT character.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcpxc">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427852028</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9euf</parentid>
<body>um wrong because they cannot do whatever they want

the shows cannot use certain characters like batman, superman, or wonder woman for whatever reason

2nd; they just killed off the dead shot and arent going to use the suicide squad anymore because of the suicide squad movie...
which really pisses me off because they set up HIVE for season 4 and dead shot could've played a key roll in it

and third Grant Gustin is awesome as the flash meanwhile Ezra Miller looks like some tranny and does not look like Barry Allan at all. 

also Agents of Shield have had some major villain set ups (Gravitron) but they keep making references to the movies which is why its in a better position when it comes to story writing.</body>
<upvotes>-8</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcpzr">
<author>nobody26</author>
<timestamp>1427852030</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxa3ot</parentid>
<body>spent all the CGI budget on those two ahha</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcr85">
<author>Dirtiimartini</author>
<timestamp>1427852085</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7t6l</parentid>
<body>I want him to play Peter Parker in the new Spider-Man movie.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcrb6">
<author>faded_jester</author>
<timestamp>1427852089</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>I gave Arrow a shot mostly cause Crixis from Spartacus was in it.(fanfuckingtastic series btw) First couple episodes I thought....oh wow they actually made a hero who would take care of business and not be a whiney bitch about killing bad guys. Low and behold it descends into...."ermagurd I can't kill people....ermagurd my feelings!" My desire to find out what happened on the island made me last until the middle of the second season.            

On a side note did anyone else notice how unbelievably judgemental almost all the women were on that show...up until *their* feelings came into play....then everything *they* did was justified. 

There are certainly worse shows on tv but I'm hoping the Daredevil show on Netflix will be the quality comic book show I've always wanted. 

Anyhoo good for Stephen, he's a pretty decent actor.</body>
<upvotes>-5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcueb">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427852234</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxc8un</parentid>
<body>[deleted]</body>
<upvotes>4</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcuna">
<author>mi_esposa_me_espia</author>
<timestamp>1427852246</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7v69</parentid>
<body>And the winner for best acting in a leading role goes to......

**black driver!!**

*thunderous applause*</body>
<upvotes>7</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcvdm">
<author>mi_esposa_me_espia</author>
<timestamp>1427852282</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx6qb6</parentid>
<body>I think he's actually pretty decent as an actor, lots of charm too.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcvts">
<author>SpartacusMcGinty</author>
<timestamp>1427852304</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7rn1</parentid>
<body>Also it has a bit of an incenstual undertone.</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcwvu">
<author>pjtheman</author>
<timestamp>1427852352</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9six</parentid>
<body>This is /r/movies.  You don't have to *see* a movie to know it sucks.  Take Batman v Superman for example.</body>
<upvotes>-1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxcyj0">
<author>SpartacusMcGinty</author>
<timestamp>1427852431</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9oyg</parentid>
<body>I do like how she's not an instant heroine. She needs to go through at least a little bit of punishment before she can be anywhere near the level of the Arrow.</body>
<upvotes>8</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxczmg">
<author>Baddboy78</author>
<timestamp>1427852482</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx8zfo</parentid>
<body>So was Katrina Law - Nyssa al Ghul,  Played Mira, Spartacus's F*ck-buddy.</body>
<upvotes>4</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd0yg">
<author>OMGALEX</author>
<timestamp>1427852547</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcueb</parentid>
<body>Hey, upvote for backing up your hate for the movie. I'm glad you watched it and have an opinion.</body>
<upvotes>4</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd3o9">
<author>TerminallyCapriSun</author>
<timestamp>1427852683</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxd0yg</parentid>
<body>I try not to hate on movies I avoid.  Like, I'd never bother to watch the Twilight series.  That sounds like a waste of time to me.  But because of that, I'm not going to go around making fun of how bad it is.  That would be unfair.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd59v">
<author>definitelylegitlol</author>
<timestamp>1427852760</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxb2qo</parentid>
<body>He goes out of his way to attend events as far as I can tell. I met him at Phoenix Comic-Con and was lovely. On facebook, he tries to let people ahead of time know that he can't make it to an event, I've also read stories of him taking redeyes and driving last minute to appear. Dude loves his fans.</body>
<upvotes>10</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd5dr">
<author>TheOtherCumKing</author>
<timestamp>1427852765</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcpxc</parentid>
<body>&gt; the shows cannot use certain characters like batman, superman, or wonder woman for whatever reason

They could. They choose not to do so for creative reasons. Those characters would overshadow the central protagonists. Also, the showrunner for Arrow is married to the showrunner of Gotham and they don't want to be stepping on each other's toes. 

&gt; 2nd; they just killed off the dead shot and arent going to use the suicide squad anymore because of the suicide squad movie

Its not so much the movie as it is the fact that they were planning to do a spinoff show for the Suicide Squad and were setting up for it. Plans for that fell through and its improbable at the moment so they probably don't see a point in focusing on it for the show. 

&gt; and third Grant Gustin is awesome as the flash meanwhile Ezra Miller looks like some tranny and does not look like Barry Allan at all.

Ezra Miller is a movie actor while Grant is a TV actor. 

&gt; also Agents of Shield have had some major villain set ups (Gravitron) but they keep making references to the movies which is why its in a better position when it comes to story writing.

Agents of Shields can get away with just making references or having cameos and still be a decent show because it is envisioned as a companion show. Imagine if they made a TV series for Superman and weren't allowed to show Lex Luthor or Batman without Joker. Flash is about a superhero and there are very specific storylines that the writers right now have the freedom to use. If you just used them and casted TV actors, no studio in the world is going to approve a multi-million dollar franchise made up of two bit TV actors and it sure as hell isn't going to sell as well.</body>
<upvotes>-1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd6xy">
<author>twent4</author>
<timestamp>1427852839</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxd59v</parentid>
<body>hey thats cool, I'm just relaying the impression my friend had.</body>
<upvotes>-6</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxd89o">
<author>Knyfe-Wrench</author>
<timestamp>1427852902</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7fq7</parentid>
<body>At first the plot holes and lack of internal consistency were pretty painful to watch. (He can move so fast that time is effectively stopped, but can't take a gun out of someone's hand?) But as the season has gone on they've gotten better about that, while simultaneously making the plots better so I don't care as much.

I think it's starting to eclipse Arrow, which has had far fewer jaw-dropping fangirl moments than last season.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxdcuw">
<author>Leftys-Wheelchair</author>
<timestamp>1427853121</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7fq7</parentid>
<body>The guy who plays the Flash...

He will be my only Flash. Whoever gets Flash on the big screen will only be a placeholder between seasons.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxdd63">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427853137</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxd5dr</parentid>
<body>actually

http://io9.com/confirmed-batman-and-superman-are-off-limits-for-arrow-1662696484</body>
<upvotes>5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxddpt">
<author>Leftys-Wheelchair</author>
<timestamp>1427853164</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7v69</parentid>
<body>"Black driver"...</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxdkwx">
<author>CoachTTP</author>
<timestamp>1427853510</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxbbko</parentid>
<body>For a movie studio, the objective is to make money. Turtles made money. They believe more turtles will make more money. Even if you didn't enjoy the movie, you'd have to be denser than a neutron star to think this wasn't going to happen.</body>
<upvotes>10</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxdn8z">
<author>Knyfe-Wrench</author>
<timestamp>1427853622</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxahi3</parentid>
<body>Oh snap, I'd love a Titans live action show.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxe01l">
<author>IwishIwasGoku</author>
<timestamp>1427854247</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxdn8z</parentid>
<body>It's already in production, so your wish has been granted!</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxe6lz">
<author>legopieface</author>
<timestamp>1427854573</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcwvu</parentid>
<body>I'm pretty sure the majority is excited for BvS. I see what you're trying to get at though.</body>
<upvotes>8</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxe9pm">
<author>legopieface</author>
<timestamp>1427854727</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9vit</parentid>
<body>He's a comic dick. He is funny and you laugh at his scenes but he's probably going to be a prick to the turtles up until A, he gets his ass kicked, or B, the climax. 

He is actually a really good mix between funny and serious. I'd imagine he'd be a good mix in tmnt 2. They did a damn good job at making the turtles likable and I'm sure they will do the same for Casey.</body>
<upvotes>5</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxefsk">
<author>pjtheman</author>
<timestamp>1427855020</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxe6lz</parentid>
<body>True some of the early "DAE AVENGERS RULES DC DROOLZZ" hate has died down.  Still, /r/movies has a funny way of judging movies before they come out.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxes9o">
<author>carbonnanotube</author>
<timestamp>1427855646</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7fq7</parentid>
<body>I tried so hard to like it, but it was just way too campy, inconsistent, and the straw that broke the camel's back so to speak was having an absolute cold gun cancel out an absolute heat gun. 

I am willing to suspend disbelief, but that was such staggeringly stupid writing (that didn't have to be that way) that I gave up on the show.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxet5a">
<author>carbonnanotube</author>
<timestamp>1427855687</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx8gfb</parentid>
<body>I don't know, the actress playing the techie girl has some great plots......</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxf05l">
<author>ILoveToEatLobster</author>
<timestamp>1427856026</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Dude doesn't look tough at all.</body>
<upvotes>-2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxf0tw">
<author>senopahx</author>
<timestamp>1427856059</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxd5dr</parentid>
<body>&gt; Ezra Miller

...was a TV actor who has done a few indy movies.  You're making him out to be way more than he is.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxf9iy">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427856489</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcpxc</parentid>
<body>We dont know for sure that deadshot is, well dead. they never found a body and because Waller assumed he was dead she probably never killed him remotely. He could be alive still. I mean for fucks sake oliver was stabbed and thrown off a cliff.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfckb">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427856643</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxet5a</parentid>
<body>But I'm tired of this forced romantic tension between her and Oliver, it just doesn't fit at all and feels wrong. I get that they are close but they should be good friends. I know she's with Palmer now but its obvious they are still trying to force that tension through Oliver and it DOES NOT WORK. outside of the shitty forced coupling, Felicity is a wonderful character.</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfedw">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427856734</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcknl</parentid>
<body>He was an amazing Slade</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfetf">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427856756</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxa30f</parentid>
<body>&gt; Jane the Virgin

I would not use this and good in a sentence together.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfg4z">
<author>carbonnanotube</author>
<timestamp>1427856825</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfckb</parentid>
<body>You know, wonderful tracts of land......</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfkh7">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427857043</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcyj0</parentid>
<body>I hate how they're letting Laurel take up her sister's mantle. She's (for the most part) untrained, acts without thinking, and the "thrill" she gets from it is just to substitute for her drug/alcohol problem of earlier seasons. She is not, and will never be the black canary.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxflv4">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427857111</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcueb</parentid>
<body>They made Mikey kinda rapey. it was unsettling</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfmsu">
<author>2-Skinny</author>
<timestamp>1427857156</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx6qb6</parentid>
<body>Too bad regardless of his performance the movie is going to be a steaming dump.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfmxb">
<author>rkkrqqqqrssss</author>
<timestamp>1427857162</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxf05l</parentid>
<body>It's because you failed the city</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfnc3">
<author>ihateworking20</author>
<timestamp>1427857182</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxc87l</parentid>
<body>Well I care because as a fan of the original source material this movie completely disgraced it. Shredder is a half ironman/brute, the footclan are a bunch of mercenaries with guns, Karai is reduced to being a useless henchman, Will Arnett, Whoopi Goldberg, and the worst of it all Megan Fox had more screen time and more to do with the whole plot (which had an extremely similar plot like Amazing Spider-Man 2) than the TMNT and Splinter. Now everything before the last part I can forgive as long they mainly focused on the turtles, but instead the focus was all about April O'Neil and how her past is the key to everything. The movie should have been called April O'Neil and the TMNT.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfojg">
<author>IAmATroyMcClure</author>
<timestamp>1427857239</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7dnd</parentid>
<body>Honestly I think Arrow has gone to shit this season. The show has always been a little dumb but the characters are so fucking unbearable. Everyone is always keeping secrets and being irrational for no reason. It feels like Gossip Girl with superheroes or some shit. And now the characters who are usually reasonable (Roy, Lance, Diggle, Felicity) barely get any dialogue or have turned melodramatic like the rest of them.

And I am usually the guy who is arguing against the whole "anti-dark and gritty" phase with comic book fans, because gritty can be a good thing, I fucking HATE how gritty that show tries to be. It's impossible to take seriously when the characters are saying stupid shit like 99% of the time in the show, or when the acting is horrible, or when the special effects look like garbage.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfpjm">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427857289</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfg4z</parentid>
<body>Oh, she's hot as shit, thats not even going to be denied. She does bring some much needed levity to the show through her silliness. And she is capable and good at what she does (even if the technobable bullshit is in fact bullshit and in no way rooted in any reality, but you know, comic books)</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxftt5">
<author>ch4dr0x</author>
<timestamp>1427857505</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxb8ur</parentid>
<body>Ashur and Varro? Finally gods remove cock from ass.</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfvqw">
<author>katniss_everjeans</author>
<timestamp>1427857605</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfkh7</parentid>
<body>&gt; She is not, and will never be the black canary.

Dinah "Laurel" Lance has been the rightful Black Canary for 65+ years, no matter how much you dislike this interpretation of the character.</body>
<upvotes>6</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfw77">
<author>whitedragon88</author>
<timestamp>1427857628</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Why are they making another one? Didn't the first one pretty much go straight to DVD?</body>
<upvotes>-2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfy7v">
<author>Jynx3</author>
<timestamp>1427857733</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>When Casey raped those guys in Oz I was so dissapointed.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxfzpm">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427857809</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfvqw</parentid>
<body>Oh, I know the context of the original character, but this interpretation of her isn't fit for the mantle. Perhaps things can change in future seasons, but as she is now the answer is still no. 

And I apologize for not specifying I meant in the context of this show.</body>
<upvotes>3</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxg5av">
<author>frahmer86</author>
<timestamp>1427858105</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcr85</parentid>
<body>Me too, but I know he's not going to.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxg6m4">
<author>RandomJPG6</author>
<timestamp>1427858173</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcknl</parentid>
<body>I'll admit I like him as Slade. But that doesn't excuse the rest of the season. It was easily the best part of the show so far but even still it's really not THAT cool. I really don't understand why people think that made up for the rest of the shitty first season. Even the first half of season two was pretty bad.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgd3r">
<author>ZensRockets</author>
<timestamp>1427858514</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx76gj</parentid>
<body>TIL producing a movie that made near half a billion is failure.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxge2k">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427858565</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx9seg</parentid>
<body>But le movies are le art and hollywood respects that.</body>
<upvotes>4</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgeoo">
<author>Butters_Thats_Me</author>
<timestamp>1427858598</timestamp>
<parentid>cpx7fq7</parentid>
<body>is it really that good? I haven't seen it, I dont really like superhero shows and stuff like that, but for some reason I love arrow, think I'd like flash even though from what i've seen i like oliver more than the flash guy(only seen flash in the arrow epsidodes)</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgf0o">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427858616</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxbwdh</parentid>
<body>Move somehow makes even more money than its predecessor.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgk2u">
<author>molemon</author>
<timestamp>1427858880</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxgeoo</parentid>
<body>The Flash gets a pretty big story set up from the beginning</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgnbk">
<author>Doro1234</author>
<timestamp>1427859057</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxcpzr</parentid>
<body>To be fair Azog's CGI is pretty damn impressive as well, it's just shame that it's only him and Smaug that look good while everyone else looks passable at best.</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgrcq">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427859275</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxf9iy</parentid>
<body>yes but the difference is 

http://screencrush.com/arrow-season-4-suicide-squad-deadshot-off-the-table/</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgsbc">
<author>Butters_Thats_Me</author>
<timestamp>1427859326</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxgk2u</parentid>
<body>hmm, okay i guess i'll give it a go, seems like it could get interesting, super speed is a pretty cool ability.

the arrow having no special powers was part of the reason i liked arrow though, but who knows, thanks man!</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgvf2">
<author>3OAM</author>
<timestamp>1427859489</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Why does he look walleyed? Gonna be hard to see out of a hockey mask with Rick-Sanchez-Burping eyes.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxgx8g">
<author>OtakuMecha</author>
<timestamp>1427859590</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfw77</parentid>
<body>It made nearly half a billion dollars.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxh4zw">
<author>Dhrakyn</author>
<timestamp>1427860011</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxa3ot</parentid>
<body>That would have made the movie suck less.  It was an experiment in how to spend gobs of cash and suck as much as possible and still be profitable.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxh94j">
<author>esephscifi</author>
<timestamp>1427860243</timestamp>
<parentid>30zbtu</parentid>
<body>Do they mean David Gordon Green?</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxh9op">
<author>rg90184</author>
<timestamp>1427860273</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxgrcq</parentid>
<body>Well thats depressing.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxhdpq">
<author>[deleted]</author>
<timestamp>1427860498</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxh9op</parentid>
<body>my point exactly</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxhr7x">
<author>noodlescb</author>
<timestamp>1427861255</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxc8un</parentid>
<body>I actually paid for a ticket to Guardians and snuck in to avoid contributing to the end dollar amount.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxhygr">
<author>vultrun</author>
<timestamp>1427861668</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfojg</parentid>
<body>I agree with you and it makes me sad to admit. This is the first season I've watched it one week at a time. Normally I wait for it on Netflix then binge it. I was just thinking maybe I was noticing the stupid subplots more because I was only getting it one episode at a time. The Flash has been the complete opposite. I've been excited in pretty much every episode of it.</body>
<upvotes>0</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxkw95">
<author>whitedragon88</author>
<timestamp>1427868586</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxgx8g</parentid>
<body>But only around 80 million was actual profit and it received almost completely negative reviews.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxm85z">
<author>Dynamiklol</author>
<timestamp>1427873249</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxfnc3</parentid>
<body>It's a fiction for kids, none of that matters. It's a movie about mutant Turtles fighting crime, it doesn't need a deep plot with character development or anything, it just needs to be fun. The first one was fun, this one will more than likely be fun.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxnc7v">
<author>OMGALEX</author>
<timestamp>1427878161</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxhr7x</parentid>
<body>Okay, that's genuinely hilarious.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxpyuy">
<author>Evanderson</author>
<timestamp>1427889854</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxddpt</parentid>
<body>That's what he refers to himself as in the show. Not racist I swear</body>
<upvotes>2</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
<post id="cpxuaft">
<author>noodlescb</author>
<timestamp>1427899809</timestamp>
<parentid>cpxnc7v</parentid>
<body>I love the franchise so I felt obligated. I just feel like children deserve better.</body>
<upvotes>1</upvotes>
<downvotes>0</downvotes>
</post>
</posts>
</thread>
</forum>
